<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ray Yang</title><link>https://rayspock.com/</link><description>Recent content on Ray Yang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><managingEditor>rayspock@protonmail.com (rayspock)</managingEditor><webMaster>rayspock@protonmail.com (rayspock)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rayspock.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How I became a developer? (Part1)</title><link>https://rayspock.com/posts/how-i-became-a-developer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>rayspock@protonmail.com (rayspock)</author><guid>https://rayspock.com/posts/how-i-became-a-developer/</guid><description>Technology is one of the most popular aspects in almost every industry. As for software technology, they have been widely used for decades. I still remember the first computer that my dad bought me which requires you to install a bunch of different software and specifically only use the operating system ‘windows 95’ in order to function properly. Yeah, it was very old that you might not hear of and the performance is slower than the smartphone people have nowadays, but it was pretty awesome back then.</description></item><item><title>How do I clear cookies for a specific site with one click?</title><link>https://rayspock.com/posts/clean-captain/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>rayspock@protonmail.com (rayspock)</author><guid>https://rayspock.com/posts/clean-captain/</guid><description>I often find that clearing cookies for the website that I’m visiting is a real annoyance because it comes with several steps to use the built-in feature that chrome provides to clear them. Besides, most of the Chrome Extensions will clear all the website data and you will lose all your login details for some websites. If you’re lucky you might be fine with signing in.
But the truth is people (at least in my experience) won’t always remember the username/password when needed.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://rayspock.com/page/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>rayspock@protonmail.com (rayspock)</author><guid>https://rayspock.com/page/about/</guid><description>I worked with different industries, including Blockchain, FinTech, Education, Healthcare and Retail, to build extraordinary things for extraordinary people. My strengths are mostly in the backend, but I can do frontend like HTML/CSS, JS (React, Redux, etc.), which enable me to create everything from small business websites to custom web applications.
Skills Tools &amp;amp; Technologies Years Experience Javascript 4 Golang 2 React 3 AWS 2 Experience Solution Architect Identified key areas of technical risk or complexity, proposed appropriate Proofs of Concepts (POCs).</description></item><item><title>Work</title><link>https://rayspock.com/page/work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>rayspock@protonmail.com (rayspock)</author><guid>https://rayspock.com/page/work/</guid><description>Projects Tools &amp;amp; Technologies Bequest Golang, CI/CD, Docker,Microservices, Kubernetes, React, Typescript Cool X Wallet Java, Netty, AWS Cloud HSM, Docker, Blockchain CoolWallet S Golang, Blockchain, CI/CD, React Native Spark API REST API, Blockchain, Python Sygna Bridge Demo React, Redux, Saga, Typescript Resumake React, Node.js, JavaScript Bequest Personalised pay-as-you-go life insurance and online wills.</description></item></channel></rss>