<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>learning-journey on Ray Yang</title><link>https://rayspock.com/tags/learning-journey/</link><description>Recent content in learning-journey on Ray Yang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><managingEditor>rayspock@protonmail.com (rayspock)</managingEditor><webMaster>rayspock@protonmail.com (rayspock)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rayspock.com/tags/learning-journey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Learn Go Pipelines by building keyword search tool</title><link>https://rayspock.com/posts/go-pipeline/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>rayspock@protonmail.com (rayspock)</author><guid>https://rayspock.com/posts/go-pipeline/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s challenge is about working with concurrency in Go - Goroutines, Channels, and Pipelines. The following exercise is from the book, “Mastering Go: Create Golang production applications using network libraries, concurrency, machine learning, and advanced data structures” by Mihalis Tsoukalos. The book not only contains a lot of useful examples and best practices but also helps you understand the capability of Go in depth via well-written descriptions. I highly recommend reading through this book to keep your Go journey going smoothly and advance your programming skill with Go.</description></item><item><title>Let's talk about smart contracts</title><link>https://rayspock.com/posts/smart-contract/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>rayspock@protonmail.com (rayspock)</author><guid>https://rayspock.com/posts/smart-contract/</guid><description>Recently, I finally finished a lecture about developing smart contracts on Blockchain which I bought from Udemy 5 months ago. To be honest, it’s been busy for me to complete a 12 hour long course over the past few months. Nevertheless, it was really great to take a deep dive into learning how to implement some famous use cases like tokenising assets or order tracking with Solidity. It was worth the effort to do it because I now feel more confident than before when I was developing smart contract projects during hackathon events.</description></item></channel></rss>